#### STATISTICAL CONSULTANT

Statistician trained at the postgraduate level in the social sciences using the R language. Trusted consultant with proven success collaborating with executive stakeholders and scientists to design, implement, analyze, and publish research and program evaluation. Use traditional, machine learning, network analysis, spatial analysis, and data visualization approaches to inquiry. Subject matter expert in organizational behavior, clinical psychology, and mental health science, with emerging skillsets in psychiatric epidemiology and urban policy & planning.

Technologies: R, R markdown - advanced | Python, Jupyter Notebook, SPSS, Tableau, PowerPoint - intermediate

### **EDUCATION**

CLAREMONT GRADUATE UNIVERSITY, Claremont, CA: Master of Arts (MA) in Organizational Behavior & Evaluation | 2020 SOFIA UNIVERSITY, Palo Alto, CA: Master of Arts (MA) in Clinical Psychology | 2013 NAROPA UNIVERSITY, Boulder, CO: Bachelor of Arts (BA) in Traditional Eastern Arts | 2010

## RECENT EXPERIENCE

## KINESIS CONSULTING, Phoenixville, PA: Principal | 01/2021 - present

Statistical consultation including social science methodology, visualization, and presentation in support of policy analysis and program evaluation for the scientific community. Focus is on methodological innovation for evaluation in support of climate change mitigation and resilience infrastructure projects. Examples of recent projects:

- Survey analysis and presentation for external program evaluation in NSF Directorate for Geosciences
- Mixed method / Social network analysis for external program evaluation in NSF Division of Undergraduate Education
- Social network analyses for external program evaluation in NSF Office of Integrative Activities.

## LISA KACZMARCZYK PHD CONSULTING, LLC, Claremont, CA: Statistical Consultant | 09/2019 – 01/2021

Statistical, survey, presentation, and peer-review authoring support of program evaluation for the sciences.

- Designed social network analysis tool used by client for external evaluation focused on critical relationships between principal investigators and other campus personnel in support of NSF Division of Undergraduate Education program.
- Participant survey analysis and presentation creation for program evaluation of NSF Earth Cube Community Office.

# ACCENTURE PLC, CGU TALENT INNOVATION LAB, Claremont, CA: Consultant | 11/2018 – 06/2020

Global HR / Recruitment Transformation Research & Development Lab

Managed project deliverable content and translated peer-reviewed organizational behavior research into business cases. High-impact example provided below.

Project: Future workplace job redesign research and market analysis for account executive role

Role: Project Lead

- Directed final project deliverables for new client, CEO's strategic advisor.
- Formulated, pitched, and executed strategy project that provided technical recommendations for assessing, developing, and predicting future developmental trends related to high-impact role of account executive. Presented results to senior leadership. Project continues in new phase with estimated completion in September 2020.
- Led project team (consultant, project manager, 2 assistants); managed performance and career development.

MOUNT SAINT MARYS UNIVERSITY, PSYCHOLOGY DEPARTMENT, Los Angeles, CA: Instructor | 01/2016 – 05/2018 Taught upper-division coursework in research methods, social psychology, and I/O psychology. Academic advisor for 25 undergraduate students with 100% graduation rate.

- Quantitative methods in coursework: basic survey methods, correlation, χ2 categorical analysis, within-subjects design, between-subjects design, single subject design, single regression
- Qualitative methods in coursework: naturalistic observation, thematic content analysis
- Additional topics: research ethics, NIH human subjects training, APA format manuscript preparation using SPSS, introduction to R language, introduction to JMV (jamovi) graphical interface for R
- Coordination of symposium and opening speech on topic of importance of promoting undergraduate research and representation of women in STEM